<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Torbjörn Molin - Blog</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Torbjörn Molin - Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 09:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AutoIt</title><link>/autoit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 09:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>/autoit/</guid><description>The last few days I&amp;rsquo;ve been running a background type task on a Windows machine that I don&amp;rsquo;t have full access to configure. What I wanted was for the machine not to go to sleep since every time that happened a VPN-connection that I needed would be disconnected and no matter what settings I changed I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get that to happen.
A quick and dirty solution came to mind, what if I just have something automatically move the mouse cursor?</description></item><item><title>A quick look at HTMX</title><link>/a-quick-look-at-htmx/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 09:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>/a-quick-look-at-htmx/</guid><description>The times they are a-changing There are trends in everything and tech stacks, programming languages and frameworks are certainly no exception, quite the opposite. Recently one of the technologies that has fallen out of favor the people that like to tell the internet what&amp;rsquo;s hot is SPA applications and client side rendered pages in general.
Thoughtworks added &amp;ldquo;SPA by default&amp;rdquo; to their hold list in march of 2022 on the grounds that teams have stoped contemplating that going with a SPA is even a choice in the first place.</description></item><item><title>Diving into .NET source</title><link>/dotnet-is-open-source/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 08:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dotnet-is-open-source/</guid><description>Once upon a time&amp;hellip; Microsoft was, as many of us remember, not always a proponent of open source and free software. In the 1990s and 2000s the company did what it could to stop open source from gaining momentum and internal memos talked about embrace-extend-extinguish as a strategy that could be adopted.
The Microsoft of today is very different and some development tools that used to be closed source and very expensive are now free in one or two senses of the word.</description></item><item><title>What are SOLID principles</title><link>/what-are-solid-principles/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 08:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>/what-are-solid-principles/</guid><description>Background A while back I was at a technical interview for a consultant assignment and the interviewer asked about SOLID principles and Clean Code. I had heard of both and read a most of Clean Code, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t list what the acronym SOLID stands for so in order to perhaps make me remember it next time I decided to write this.
SOLID is an acronym for a set of principles for development of object oriented software promoted by &amp;lsquo;Uncle&amp;rsquo; Bob Martin who also wrote Clean Code.</description></item><item><title>Picking a static site generator</title><link>/picking-a-static-site-generator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 13:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>/picking-a-static-site-generator/</guid><description>A bit of background I&amp;rsquo;ve had this domain for a bit over a decade now and use it for a number of email accounts. Years ago there used to be a Wordpress blog on here about live sound engineering and now that I work as a developer and also recently started freelancing, I felt that now would be a good time to get a new site up.
Just pick something! I tried (I really did) not to get too caught up in picking a platform for managing it, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to use Wordpress again, it felt clunky and overkill.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/page/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>/page/about/</guid><description>About I&amp;rsquo;m a freelance software developer based in Gothenburg, Sweden. I mainly do backend work in C# and .NET with the occasional frontend bits in javascript or typescript with one of the major frameworks. I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested in computers since my dad first bought an IBM 386 PC when I six or seven years old and programming has been with me in various forms almost since then.</description></item><item><title>Recommended reading</title><link>/reccomended-reading/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>/reccomended-reading/</guid><description>About the list This is a compilation of some of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve read and some videos that I like and also some things that are on my list that I haven&amp;rsquo;t gotten to yet. I think that some of it may be useful for people like me who are interested in and perhaps work with computers, programming and computer science but are self taught.
Programming from the ground up by Jonathan Bartlett This free (available here under the GNU Free documentation license) really is what the title says.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/page/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>/page/contact/</guid><description>Contact Aenean ipsum justo, semper eu nisl ut, pretium tincidunt sem. Praesent et diam sit amet lacus lobortis dictum a id lacus. Quisque hendrerit sit amet turpis eu varius. Ut id lorem ac felis ultrices tincidunt. Pellentesque consequat arcu ac fringilla imperdiet. Phasellus pellentesque, sapien non pulvinar blandit, sapien ante aliquet felis, vel porttitor sapien ante in lacus. Fusce non urna aliquet, malesuada nibh vel, luctus urna. Phasellus ut lacus molestie, varius purus quis, malesuada lorem.</description></item></channel></rss>