<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Torbjörn Molin - Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Torbjörn Molin - Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 02:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/about/</guid>
      <description>About I&amp;rsquo;m a freelance software developer based in Gothenburg, Sweden. I mainly do backend work in C# and .NET with the occasional frontend bits in javascript or typescript with one of the major frameworks. I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested in computers since my dad first bought an IBM 386 PC when I six or seven years old and programming has been with me in various forms almost since then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommended reading</title>
      <link>/reccomended-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reccomended-reading/</guid>
      <description>About the list This is a compilation of some of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve read and some videos that I like and also some things that are on my list that I haven&amp;rsquo;t gotten to yet. I think that some of it may be useful for people like me who are interested in and perhaps work with computers, programming and computer science but are self taught.
Programming from the ground up by Jonathan Bartlett This free (available here under the GNU Free documentation license) really is what the title says.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Aenean ipsum justo, semper eu nisl ut, pretium tincidunt sem. Praesent et diam sit amet lacus lobortis dictum a id lacus. Quisque hendrerit sit amet turpis eu varius. Ut id lorem ac felis ultrices tincidunt. Pellentesque consequat arcu ac fringilla imperdiet. Phasellus pellentesque, sapien non pulvinar blandit, sapien ante aliquet felis, vel porttitor sapien ante in lacus. Fusce non urna aliquet, malesuada nibh vel, luctus urna. Phasellus ut lacus molestie, varius purus quis, malesuada lorem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
